Muhammad Rizal

Surabaya, East Java, Indonesia muhammadrizal15122001@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadrizalgg/ https://mehmed-profile.vercel.app

I am a student at the Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya. I majored in Informatics Engineering. I am interested in the fields of Frontend, Mobile and Backend development. For studies, I have experience in Flutter Mobile, Software Quality Assurance, and served as Assistant Product Owner of Simple Wallet. I also have experience in Frontend and Backend development.

Experience

Backend Developer • Intern CV Sejahtera Mandiri Solusindo

Dec 2023 - present | Surabaya, Indonesia

- Responsible for handling backend software.
- Create an API with JavaScript Express.
- Designing the data layout in the database.
- Worked on connecting backend with Next JS frontend.

Assistant Product Owner • Agile Teknik

February 2023 - November 2023 | Surabaya, Indonesia

- Coordinate the Simple Wallet team with the product to identify bottlenecks in product development.
- I was assigned to Software Quality Assurance.
- I provide assistance to Flutter based Mobile developers.
- I am involved in creating a PHP Laravel based backend system.

Steering Committee of Major Orientation

Juny 2022 - January 2023 | Surabaya, Indonesia

- I collaborated with the information engineering student association to create a concept for a major orientation event.
- I provided guidance to the committee for the introduction to the department.

Frontend Developer • E - code

December 2021 - May 2023 | Surabaya, Indonesia

- I worked on the front end of the e-voting project for the election of chairman of the Informatics Engineering Student Association.
- This project uses PHP Laravel.

Education

Politeknik Elektronika Negeri Surabaya

Informatics Enginering • 2021 - present

Skills

- Backend Developer
- Software Quality Assurance
- Mobile Developer
- Frontend Developer

Languages

- Indonesia: Native speaker
- English: Intermediate speaker

Powered by CakeResume